sotite.com 2012-06-06

# Security & Privacy Policy | SoTite

### SoTite takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

### This policy covers how the company treats personal information that is collected when visitors create an account with SoTite.  

### When you register we ask for information such as your email address, birthday, gender, and zip code.  

### SoTite uses this information to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill our promotions and sweepstakes promises, and improve our services.  

## INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

### SoTite does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  

### We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  

### We may transfer information about you if the Company is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, the Company will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  

### The Company may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.  

### The Company does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.  

### We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to SoTite’s services, such as service announcements, and administrative messages, that are considered part of your SoTite account.  

## CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

### We limit access to personal information about you to employees or contractors with whom we have confidentiality agreements, and who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.  

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

### SoTite may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your SoTite account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.  

## QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS

### If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at [admin@sotite.com](mailto:admin@sotite.com).
